Hello guys, welcome back to my channel.  How
are you all?  So guys, today in this video
I am going to share with you the vacancies of two different banks.
You must have
seen it in the thumbnail.  Ok?  So
anyone can apply for it.
I will give you all the details later.  There are going to be vacancies in bulk.
Ok?
I will tell you about each vacancy one by one.   The
important thing is that
both these vacancies are going to be work from office vacancies.
So, people who live around Mumbai,
all the people of Mumbai
live in the nearby locations of Mumbai
or there is a vacancy for a Vashi.  Ok?
So only those people who belong to these two locations should
continue watching this video.
Otherwise you can leave the video.
Ok?  Because both these
vacancies are at Mumbai location.
Mumbai and Vashi only.  Ok?  So let's
start the video.  But before that,
if you are new to this channel, then quickly go and
subscribe to the channel and
also press the bell icon, due to which
you will get the notification of all the videos
first.  Ok?  So let's get
[music]
started.  So guys, as I
told you today I am going to
share two different bank vacancies with you.
A not exactly bank vacancies
but bank is in process.  Ok?  So first of all,
one is from Kotak Bank and the other is from
ICICI Insurance sector which is
ICICI LB.  Ok?  So the first
vacancy in the first bank is
in Kotak Bank.
This job will be in the process of Kotak Bank.  Ok?  So a
total of 170 vacancies have been released in it.
Ok?  So this work of BPO,
generally calling cross selling, will be
your work.  Ok?  So this vacancy is in
Navi Mumbai and then all the areas of Mumbai
like Manjwada, Thane
, Kalyan, Bhiwandi, Mulund, Ullasnagar,
Amarnath.  Ok?  If you belong to all these areas then
you
can apply for this vacancy.  Because the
location of this vacancy is, if you get
selected then your location will be
just a minute, so your location will be
Kapur Bawdi Majiwada
Kapur Bawdi Junction Majiwada Thane,
so if you are nearby from here
or you can go here, if you
can go for a job daily, then there is a vacancy for you, so
in this vacancy, even if you are 12th pass,
you can still apply.  12th pass graduate
is ok?  Anyone can apply for this.
Freshers can apply.  Those who have
some experience can also
apply for this.  If you have
experience then its plus point is
that you
get a little more salary than your salary.  Ok?  According to the
freshers.  After that,
anyone who can join it immediately can
apply for it because
they need immediate joiners.
If we talk about your work, even if your
communication skills are average, it will still work.  There is
no need for such a You Know excellent communication skill.
If your English is good, your Hindi
is good, your Marathi is good then you
can apply for the job.  Ok?  Ah, if we
talk about its salary, then
you will get a salary ranging from Rs 14,000 to Rs 20,000
depending on your experience.  Ok?  And along with that
you will also get incentives.  If
you apply for any bank process
, apply for any work
, if it is related to the bank then you have to do some
cross selling.
Ok?  So cross selling means that
if you sell any other products of Kotak, then accordingly
incentives will also be added
to your salary.  Otherwise your salary will be between Rs
14,000 to Rs 20,000.
Ok?  So those who are interested in this, they should
quickly go and apply.
I have already given its link in the description.
So please check the description.
And if you have any problem in this then
you can comment me.  Ok?
I will answer your comment right there.
Now let's talk about the next vacancy.
So the next vacancy is
in the insurance sector, there is a vacancy for ICICI
Lombard, which works in insurance.
Ok?  You know there is a
vacancy in his department.  So
if he has not talked about your English communication anywhere in this.
If your
Marathi and Hindi communication skills are good
then you can apply for this.  No need
of English communication.  Ok?  Because
your clients will generally be
Marathi or Hindi speaking.
Because you are working in India,
generally in Maharashtra.  Ok?  Their
location is Vashi.  So the community of Vashi
generally understands Marathi and Hindi
very well.  So
that is why if you are very good in both the languages
then you can apply for it.   It is the
same here that if you have passed 12th
then you can apply for it.
Anyone with freshers and experience can apply for this.
Male female.  Ok?  In this, only the age
criteria has been given as additional.   In
which only people in the age group of 18 to 35 can
apply.
People between the age of 18 to 35 can apply for this.
Above 35 not eligible.  Ok?  Even if your
qualification is 12th, you
can still apply for this.  No experience is
needed.  Even if you are a fresher, you
can still apply for this.  Right now you are
not going to have any exam in this, not the one
I told you about Kotak vacancy earlier.
What do you have to do in both?  If there
was a vacancy in Kotak, then you can
apply directly from the link given there.  So your resume will go to
them.  And in this vacancy, the
number of HHR is directly given.
You can WhatsApp the HR.  Ok?
And if your interview is scheduled and
if you crack the interview then
you will be selected.  There are
no exams in both.  There are no targets.
Ok?  There is no fee.  There is only a simple
interview in the selection procedure.  And that's it.
And there is nothing else.  Ok?
So here is today's update.  If you want to
know any other update apart from this, then
please mention me in the comments.  I will
bring videos for you accordingly.
I have already put the links of both
in the description.  So do
check the description.  Please do apply.
Ok?  And if guys are
with you, there are many people in India
who need jobs.  A start is
needed.  Ok?  So you can
share this video of mine with them.
You can share it with anyone.
Be it male, female,
housewives, retired persons,
students, you
can share this video with anyone because this
vacancy is for everyone.  Ok?  Anyone can
apply for this.  So quickly
go and share the video with all your friends and family.
If you
like this video, please like the video.
And don't forget to subscribe to
the channel.  Thank you so much.  Bye.